const level10Subquestions = [
  {
    "question": "76 - 50 = ?",
    "options": ["42", "20", "38", "26"],
    "answer": "26"
  },
  {
    "question": "90 - 81 = ?",
    "options": ["1", "9", "29", "19"],
    "answer": "9"
  },
  {
    "question": "49 - 39 = ?",
    "options": ["10", "20", "11", "15"],
    "answer": "10"
  },
  {
    "question": "93 - 42 = ?",
    "options": ["52", "51", "40", "62"],
    "answer": "51"
  },
  {
    "question": "96 - 89 = ?",
    "options": ["7", "-7", "-1", "15"],
    "answer": "7"
  },
  {
    "question": "63 - 54 = ?",
    "options": ["29", "-6", "9", "24"],
    "answer": "9"
  },
  {
    "question": "75 - 11 = ?",
    "options": ["64", "50", "81", "63"],
    "answer": "64"
  },
  {
    "question": "82 - 46 = ?",
    "options": ["36", "32", "51", "31"],
    "answer": "36"
  },
  {
    "question": "80 - 54 = ?",
    "options": ["40", "26", "9", "22"],
    "answer": "26"
  },
  {
    "question": "36 - 33 = ?",
    "options": ["-6", "19", "0", "3"],
    "answer": "3"
  },
  {
    "question": "69 - 19 = ?",
    "options": ["45", "50", "70", "61"],
    "answer": "50"
  },
  {
    "question": "86 - 37 = ?",
    "options": ["44", "49", "64", "51"],
    "answer": "49"
  },
  {
    "question": "98 - 21 = ?",
    "options": ["92", "79", "65", "77"],
    "answer": "77"
  },
  {
    "question": "81 - 70 = ?",
    "options": ["20", "2", "4", "11"],
    "answer": "11"
  },
  {
    "question": "45 - 39 = ?",
    "options": ["11", "-3", "10", "6"],
    "answer": "6"
  },
  {
    "question": "65 - 58 = ?",
    "options": ["7", "19", "22", "14"],
    "answer": "7"
  },
  {
    "question": "99 - 36 = ?",
    "options": ["46", "63", "78", "43"],
    "answer": "63"
  },
  {
    "question": "67 - 12 = ?",
    "options": ["58", "55", "60", "38"],
    "answer": "55"
  },
  {
    "question": "32 - 31 = ?",
    "options": ["1", "12", "-3", "-18"],
    "answer": "1"
  },
  {
    "question": "61 - 45 = ?",
    "options": ["11", "-4", "36", "16"],
    "answer": "16"
  },
  {
    "question": "96 - 89 = ?",
    "options": ["-8", "5", "20", "7"],
    "answer": "7"
  },
  {
    "question": "55 - 15 = ?",
    "options": ["40", "59", "27", "58"],
    "answer": "40"
  },
  {
    "question": "50 - 11 = ?",
    "options": ["39", "31", "34", "23"],
    "answer": "39"
  },
  {
    "question": "87 - 10 = ?",
    "options": ["84", "92", "77", "95"],
    "answer": "77"
  },
  {
    "question": "81 - 48 = ?",
    "options": ["33", "36", "48", "38"],
    "answer": "33"
  },
  {
    "question": "87 - 10 = ?",
    "options": ["68", "76", "77", "85"],
    "answer": "77"
  },
  {
    "question": "83 - 27 = ?",
    "options": ["56", "53", "73", "71"],
    "answer": "56"
  },
  {
    "question": "31 - 24 = ?",
    "options": ["10", "7", "18", "25"],
    "answer": "7"
  },
  {
    "question": "65 - 54 = ?",
    "options": ["29", "24", "13", "11"],
    "answer": "11"
  },
  {
    "question": "81 - 11 = ?",
    "options": ["70", "50", "78", "57"],
    "answer": "70"
  },
  {
    "question": "59 - 16 = ?",
    "options": ["43", "51", "52", "30"],
    "answer": "43"
  },
  {
    "question": "80 - 66 = ?",
    "options": ["15", "14", "12", "10"],
    "answer": "14"
  },
  {
    "question": "93 - 28 = ?",
    "options": ["65", "52", "84", "66"],
    "answer": "65"
  },
  {
    "question": "83 - 70 = ?",
    "options": ["25", "4", "18", "13"],
    "answer": "13"
  },
  {
    "question": "63 - 34 = ?",
    "options": ["36", "29", "9", "24"],
    "answer": "29"
  },
  {
    "question": "58 - 29 = ?",
    "options": ["13", "42", "29", "26"],
    "answer": "29"
  },
  {
    "question": "62 - 42 = ?",
    "options": ["24", "17", "20", "1"],
    "answer": "20"
  },
  {
    "question": "83 - 35 = ?",
    "options": ["48", "36", "57", "68"],
    "answer": "48"
  },
  {
    "question": "83 - 54 = ?",
    "options": ["19", "49", "47", "29"],
    "answer": "29"
  },
  {
    "question": "97 - 90 = ?",
    "options": ["5", "2", "7", "-7"],
    "answer": "7"
  },
  {
    "question": "54 - 16 = ?",
    "options": ["18", "38", "25", "55"],
    "answer": "38"
  },
  {
    "question": "36 - 19 = ?",
    "options": ["12", "16", "17", "32"],
    "answer": "17"
  },
  {
    "question": "28 - 27 = ?",
    "options": ["17", "12", "15", "1"],
    "answer": "1"
  },
  {
    "question": "86 - 46 = ?",
    "options": ["40", "57", "58", "41"],
    "answer": "40"
  },
  {
    "question": "90 - 11 = ?",
    "options": ["70", "99", "79", "61"],
    "answer": "79"
  },
  {
    "question": "46 - 35 = ?",
    "options": ["-3", "12", "21", "11"],
    "answer": "11"
  },
  {
    "question": "95 - 16 = ?",
    "options": ["79", "95", "83", "96"],
    "answer": "79"
  },
  {
    "question": "52 - 30 = ?",
    "options": ["18", "22", "42", "13"],
    "answer": "22"
  },
  {
    "question": "70 - 60 = ?",
    "options": ["14", "24", "10", "7"],
    "answer": "10"
  },
  {
    "question": "28 - 26 = ?",
    "options": ["2", "12", "-4", "3"],
    "answer": "2"
  },
  {
    "question": "891 - 286 = ?",
    "options": ["594", "621", "618", "605"],
    "answer": "605"
  },
  {
    "question": "705 - 564 = ?",
    "options": ["145", "141", "146", "134"],
    "answer": "141"
  },
  {
    "question": "785 - 695 = ?",
    "options": ["90", "71", "103", "82"],
    "answer": "90"
  },
  {
    "question": "834 - 393 = ?",
    "options": ["429", "441", "423", "438"],
    "answer": "441"
  },
  {
    "question": "880 - 350 = ?",
    "options": ["549", "520", "530", "513"],
    "answer": "530"
  },
  {
    "question": "593 - 522 = ?",
    "options": ["87", "63", "71", "81"],
    "answer": "71"
  },
  {
    "question": "737 - 647 = ?",
    "options": ["82", "75", "100", "90"],
    "answer": "90"
  },
  {
    "question": "581 - 258 = ?",
    "options": ["308", "335", "323", "310"],
    "answer": "323"
  },
  {
    "question": "777 - 176 = ?",
    "options": ["601", "605", "590", "619"],
    "answer": "601"
  },
  {
    "question": "461 - 434 = ?",
    "options": ["42", "19", "27", "43"],
    "answer": "27"
  },
  {
    "question": "438 - 191 = ?",
    "options": ["231", "247", "227", "243"],
    "answer": "247"
  },
  {
    "question": "177 - 157 = ?",
    "options": ["14", "20", "34", "8"],
    "answer": "20"
  },
  {
    "question": "270 - 169 = ?",
    "options": ["82", "92", "101", "108"],
    "answer": "101"
  },
  {
    "question": "816 - 106 = ?",
    "options": ["694", "708", "710", "720"],
    "answer": "710"
  },
  {
    "question": "780 - 723 = ?",
    "options": ["67", "57", "45", "59"],
    "answer": "57"
  },
  {
    "question": "804 - 365 = ?",
    "options": ["450", "451", "439", "426"],
    "answer": "439"
  },
  {
    "question": "924 - 746 = ?",
    "options": ["172", "178", "164", "176"],
    "answer": "178"
  },
  {
    "question": "531 - 455 = ?",
    "options": ["79", "73", "76", "72"],
    "answer": "76"
  },
  {
    "question": "770 - 125 = ?",
    "options": ["645", "649", "662", "663"],
    "answer": "645"
  },
  {
    "question": "937 - 441 = ?",
    "options": ["486", "496", "480", "501"],
    "answer": "496"
  },
  {
    "question": "496 - 432 = ?",
    "options": ["64", "80", "48", "83"],
    "answer": "64"
  },
  {
    "question": "835 - 175 = ?",
    "options": ["666", "643", "669", "660"],
    "answer": "660"
  },
  {
    "question": "778 - 569 = ?",
    "options": ["203", "218", "213", "209"],
    "answer": "209"
  },
  {
    "question": "612 - 165 = ?",
    "options": ["447", "446", "435", "444"],
    "answer": "447"
  },
  {
    "question": "734 - 624 = ?",
    "options": ["116", "107", "90", "110"],
    "answer": "110"
  },
  {
    "question": "596 - 441 = ?",
    "options": ["150", "160", "155", "137"],
    "answer": "155"
  },
  {
    "question": "893 - 432 = ?",
    "options": ["478", "445", "469", "461"],
    "answer": "461"
  },
  {
    "question": "764 - 324 = ?",
    "options": ["426", "453", "420", "440"],
    "answer": "440"
  },
  {
    "question": "819 - 218 = ?",
    "options": ["611", "588", "589", "601"],
    "answer": "601"
  },
  {
    "question": "592 - 419 = ?",
    "options": ["162", "165", "173", "170"],
    "answer": "173"
  },
  {
    "question": "951 - 443 = ?",
    "options": ["518", "496", "492", "508"],
    "answer": "508"
  },
  {
    "question": "512 - 286 = ?",
    "options": ["217", "226", "219", "220"],
    "answer": "226"
  },
  {
    "question": "739 - 160 = ?",
    "options": ["597", "579", "569", "561"],
    "answer": "579"
  },
  {
    "question": "574 - 126 = ?",
    "options": ["456", "448", "444", "438"],
    "answer": "448"
  },
  {
    "question": "804 - 768 = ?",
    "options": ["36", "50", "48", "44"],
    "answer": "36"
  },
  {
    "question": "520 - 174 = ?",
    "options": ["329", "364", "346", "344"],
    "answer": "346"
  },
  {
    "question": "716 - 395 = ?",
    "options": ["319", "321", "324", "314"],
    "answer": "321"
  },
  {
    "question": "933 - 599 = ?",
    "options": ["326", "351", "329", "334"],
    "answer": "334"
  },
  {
    "question": "435 - 181 = ?",
    "options": ["254", "241", "240", "266"],
    "answer": "254"
  },
  {
    "question": "832 - 346 = ?",
    "options": ["501", "466", "486", "482"],
    "answer": "486"
  },
  {
    "question": "820 - 327 = ?",
    "options": ["493", "473", "486", "483"],
    "answer": "493"
  },
  {
    "question": "714 - 665 = ?",
    "options": ["42", "54", "47", "49"],
    "answer": "49"
  },
  {
    "question": "564 - 250 = ?",
    "options": ["297", "304", "314", "318"],
    "answer": "314"
  },
  {
    "question": "734 - 200 = ?",
    "options": ["533", "517", "538", "534"],
    "answer": "534"
  },
  {
    "question": "837 - 149 = ?",
    "options": ["688", "670", "681", "682"],
    "answer": "688"
  },
  {
    "question": "942 - 555 = ?",
    "options": ["388", "371", "387", "399"],
    "answer": "387"
  },
  {
    "question": "523 - 172 = ?",
    "options": ["358", "351", "352", "343"],
    "answer": "351"
  },
  {
    "question": "943 - 140 = ?",
    "options": ["803", "784", "790", "798"],
    "answer": "803"
  },
  {
    "question": "750 - 299 = ?",
    "options": ["459", "451", "438", "470"],
    "answer": "451"
  },
  {
    "question": "844 - 812 = ?",
    "options": ["41", "44", "32", "49"],
    "answer": "32"
  },
  {
    "question": "4986 - 2014 = ?",
    "options": ["2972", "2976", "2983", "2966"],
    "answer": "2972"
  },
  {
    "question": "7778 - 4383 = ?",
    "options": ["3407", "3396", "3394", "3395"],
    "answer": "3395"
  },
  {
    "question": "3559 - 1073 = ?",
    "options": ["2468", "2486", "2480", "2484"],
    "answer": "2486"
  },
  {
    "question": "7932 - 3543 = ?",
    "options": ["4373", "4392", "4389", "4407"],
    "answer": "4389"
  },
  {
    "question": "9916 - 6831 = ?",
    "options": ["3072", "3090", "3085", "3093"],
    "answer": "3085"
  },
  {
    "question": "8576 - 8442 = ?",
    "options": ["121", "140", "134", "141"],
    "answer": "134"
  },
  {
    "question": "6269 - 5414 = ?",
    "options": ["835", "838", "855", "859"],
    "answer": "855"
  },
  {
    "question": "3377 - 2999 = ?",
    "options": ["398", "378", "362", "364"],
    "answer": "378"
  },
  {
    "question": "5377 - 3543 = ?",
    "options": ["1834", "1817", "1838", "1835"],
    "answer": "1834"
  },
  {
    "question": "9126 - 4166 = ?",
    "options": ["4963", "4974", "4960", "4968"],
    "answer": "4960"
  },
  {
    "question": "9552 - 4018 = ?",
    "options": ["5520", "5525", "5542", "5534"],
    "answer": "5534"
  },
  {
    "question": "3750 - 2943 = ?",
    "options": ["807", "812", "816", "797"],
    "answer": "807"
  },
  {
    "question": "7730 - 3750 = ?",
    "options": ["3974", "3987", "3980", "3965"],
    "answer": "3980"
  },
  {
    "question": "5818 - 2757 = ?",
    "options": ["3045", "3043", "3061", "3078"],
    "answer": "3061"
  },
  {
    "question": "3101 - 1501 = ?",
    "options": ["1597", "1600", "1583", "1587"],
    "answer": "1600"
  },
  {
    "question": "9411 - 3554 = ?",
    "options": ["5857", "5869", "5853", "5840"],
    "answer": "5857"
  },
  {
    "question": "9417 - 7454 = ?",
    "options": ["1963", "1972", "1957", "1980"],
    "answer": "1963"
  },
  {
    "question": "6793 - 2028 = ?",
    "options": ["4749", "4765", "4750", "4776"],
    "answer": "4765"
  },
  {
    "question": "6647 - 6158 = ?",
    "options": ["499", "489", "469", "497"],
    "answer": "489"
  },
  {
    "question": "9656 - 3610 = ?",
    "options": ["6060", "6065", "6031", "6046"],
    "answer": "6046"
  },
  {
    "question": "7361 - 1746 = ?",
    "options": ["5631", "5601", "5608", "5615"],
    "answer": "5615"
  },
  {
    "question": "7675 - 5471 = ?",
    "options": ["2198", "2215", "2184", "2204"],
    "answer": "2204"
  },
  {
    "question": "8747 - 3092 = ?",
    "options": ["5657", "5655", "5650", "5637"],
    "answer": "5655"
  },
  {
    "question": "6547 - 1244 = ?",
    "options": ["5304", "5322", "5308", "5303"],
    "answer": "5303"
  },
  {
    "question": "7684 - 2932 = ?",
    "options": ["4753", "4752", "4770", "4733"],
    "answer": "4752"
  },
  {
    "question": "8720 - 2598 = ?",
    "options": ["6126", "6122", "6114", "6137"],
    "answer": "6122"
  },
  {
    "question": "3091 - 2666 = ?",
    "options": ["440", "445", "425", "428"],
    "answer": "425"
  },
  {
    "question": "4587 - 4000 = ?",
    "options": ["584", "587", "602", "589"],
    "answer": "587"
  },
  {
    "question": "7585 - 6672 = ?",
    "options": ["933", "907", "913", "929"],
    "answer": "913"
  },
  {
    "question": "6358 - 4893 = ?",
    "options": ["1458", "1469", "1465", "1463"],
    "answer": "1465"
  },
  {
    "question": "9451 - 8845 = ?",
    "options": ["606", "608", "623", "600"],
    "answer": "606"
  },
  {
    "question": "5220 - 4210 = ?",
    "options": ["997", "1024", "1003", "1010"],
    "answer": "1010"
  },
  {
    "question": "3499 - 2522 = ?",
    "options": ["977", "990", "988", "972"],
    "answer": "977"
  },
  {
    "question": "9564 - 5048 = ?",
    "options": ["4512", "4527", "4516", "4528"],
    "answer": "4516"
  },
  {
    "question": "8791 - 4642 = ?",
    "options": ["4158", "4149", "4167", "4139"],
    "answer": "4149"
  },
  {
    "question": "7902 - 4990 = ?",
    "options": ["2912", "2893", "2914", "2899"],
    "answer": "2912"
  },
  {
    "question": "4380 - 3722 = ?",
    "options": ["658", "638", "643", "647"],
    "answer": "658"
  },
  {
    "question": "6371 - 3034 = ?",
    "options": ["3352", "3337", "3321", "3339"],
    "answer": "3337"
  },
  {
    "question": "7481 - 3420 = ?",
    "options": ["4061", "4065", "4073", "4062"],
    "answer": "4061"
  },
  {
    "question": "5138 - 3010 = ?",
    "options": ["2111", "2122", "2128", "2142"],
    "answer": "2128"
  },
  {
    "question": "3231 - 1749 = ?",
    "options": ["1482", "1470", "1475", "1465"],
    "answer": "1482"
  },
  {
    "question": "8918 - 7048 = ?",
    "options": ["1873", "1870", "1864", "1868"],
    "answer": "1870"
  },
  {
    "question": "8983 - 6308 = ?",
    "options": ["2694", "2675", "2659", "2672"],
    "answer": "2675"
  },
  {
    "question": "4992 - 4552 = ?",
    "options": ["431", "458", "440", "451"],
    "answer": "440"
  },
  {
    "question": "6521 - 2037 = ?",
    "options": ["4472", "4484", "4478", "4499"],
    "answer": "4484"
  },
  {
    "question": "6520 - 4940 = ?",
    "options": ["1566", "1599", "1562", "1580"],
    "answer": "1580"
  },
  {
    "question": "7270 - 3003 = ?",
    "options": ["4267", "4255", "4254", "4253"],
    "answer": "4267"
  },
  {
    "question": "2682 - 1275 = ?",
    "options": ["1407", "1395", "1404", "1416"],
    "answer": "1407"
  },
  {
    "question": "3599 - 3243 = ?",
    "options": ["367", "343", "349", "356"],
    "answer": "356"
  },
  {
    "question": "7703 - 6910 = ?",
    "options": ["793", "795", "802", "776"],
    "answer": "793"
  }
  
];

export default level10Subquestions;